But at the point that we decided that we were all going to be equal,
but we need to talk about what equal looks like, what equity looks like.
And so then we still go back to our founding principles.
If we now are a part of the equation,
then how do we get America to live up to the beautiful that it is promised to be?
Or that it promised white men to be.
Correct. Correct. Right?
Yeah. I mean, because we're supposed to be on the same level as we are.
Yeah, yeah.
But we're not.
And we're talking about all white men get treated better than we do.
And these are just facts, right?
And when I say this, and that's not to be sounding radical, that's to be real.
No, that's...
Because when a white man rolls down the street,
he's not as concerned when he gets pulled over.
In fact, half the time, if they get pulled over
and they know they haven't done any wrong,
or if they have done something wrong, they are indignant.
They got attitudes, all kinds of stuff.
Do you know who I am?
They will go in, right?
Have you met my father?
Exactly. You'll get all of that type of energy.
But when a black person, it's like,
well, you didn't follow all the commands and you lose your life.
Yeah, yeah.
So, for me, I'm seeing you in a short term,
and that's not true.
But I'm listening to this world.
I already went through something new.
I was talking about having to be...
I got my brain and I got my brain and I got my brain,
and I got my brain and I got my brain and I had my brain.
I was like, well, what do you have to do with that?
I got my brain and I just got my brain.
I got my brain and I got my brain,
and I got my brain next to it.